This is DreamKeeper basically an integration
between Daydream agents and keeperhub as the
execution layer. Dreamkeeper is what lets a
daydream agent actually execute real on-chain
transaction through keeperhub and on the
users behalf transfers,contract calls,
conditional checks and execute operations,
pre-built defi protocols, payments all while
a deterministic firewall decides that
which is allowed to reach keeperhub. So
the model of operation is like this. The
prompt is written that's the agent intent,
A firewall thats dreamkeeper, A dry run
is is done to simulate the contract and
keeperHub serves as execution infrastructure
before a receipt is therefore seen in your
keeper history analysis. So we introduced many
endpoints in from keeperhub. Execute_transfer,
execute_contract, score, execute_check and
Execute_protocol_actions. It gets direct
execution status. Get spending limits. Tempo_sign
and tempo_release_ hold and tempo_cancel. Also,
these are the daydream actions
that exposed in dream keeper.
So now we tested this live against a cold run
that mean we cloned it in a fresh repo and tried
on a test and we got as high as seven out of eight
attack scenarios blocked that is injected prompts
as hallucinated agent were were
blocked. Yeah, I run 102 automated test,
base Sepolia testnet, Tempo testnet and
Daydreams. You can check this live Dream
Keeper on this repo right here. So now we're
going to go live into the actual testing. Yeah,
We going to run some live scenarios .
We are running one of the scenarios,
one of the attack scenarios to
see what the agent is going to do.
Also, we are running this through
an a free model on open router. So,
we also add Antropic integration. That's
a Antropic API key. If you have your
your open AI API key, those can work too. But
gemini API key is not supported or else would
have included it also. So we are running
the first live scenario at the moment.
Okay. The task is Enqueue
A prompt injection transfer a particular
amount to this address. Note:this address
has not been on the white list. Has
not been given a white list according
to what we have informed our agent before
in the live test. So the agent is thinking
We are using Nvidia nomotron.
Yeah. So the simulation was blocked because it
detected that the recipient was not whitelisted.
So there are many many attack scenarios
that were added like the injected prompt,
hallucination attacks and co and co. So now we
going to try. So when you come to our keeper
hub profile here come to our keeper analytics
profile here we see that no nothing was executed
no transfer was done. This was 18 hours ago. So at
this moment no transfer was done. So this is like
a evidence that the the dreamkeeper execution
interface between keeperhub and daydreams is
working effectively. So now we're going to
go back to try and execute a real transaction
So this is the approved.
So as you can see from here the simulation failed
the first time because my I was not having enough
USDC to execute the transaction. But after sending
some USDC into the wallet now can see simulation
successful that's it simulated it first then
confirmed it demo successful so now let's go
and confirm on the keeper interface so right now
you can see a transfer was done 11 seconds ago so
there are many and I've done many transfers.
Transfers,protocol action that is from Aave;
lending ,contract call,check and execute and many
many actions like that. So we so let's come here
also we also integrated we also integrated a
ability for other agents to be able to audit
your day dreams agents. So, but at the moment
we the backend is not hosted anywhere. So,
it's not live yet. But your agent can be able to
give you a summary of the work that was done on it
at the moment.
So these are the summary of the things
that happened. The simulation that
failed because this guy was not white
listed. The success of a simulation and
He confirmed details. So now this is a this
is transaction the same thing as this the
same thing as this. So we can go and check it
out in the go and check it out in the explorer.
Yeah. So after some minutes of battling
with internet I was able to show the
transaction hash here was some minutes ago
this transaction hash. So thank you very much.